{"data":[{"question":"She regretted ________ how to ride a bicycle when she was young.","a":"not to learn","b":"not learning","c":"not having learnt","d":"b & c are correct","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Regret+ To Verb: Feel regret for something you are going to do.\u00a0\n- Regret + Verb-ing: Feel regret for something already happened.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The doctor showed the patient ________ to do some exercises.","a":"what","b":"why","c":"when","d":"how","answer":"4","explain":"\n- To show somebody how to do something: used to ask or talk about the way in which something happens or is done.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The doctor told his friend all about ________ the woman and asked him for his advice.","a":"meet","b":"meeting","c":"to meet","d":"he met","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Preposition + Verb-ing\/noun\/noun phrase.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"If I had taken your advice, I ________ a better life.","a":"will have","b":"shall have","c":"would have","d":"would have had","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Conditional sentence type 3: If + past perfect, would\/could\/should + have + PP.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"We have got high inflation. That's why prices keep ________ up.","a":"go","b":"to go","c":"going","d":"to going","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Keep (on) doing something: to continue doing something or to do the same thing many times.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"They wanted to know why they ________ it for her while she could do it by herself","a":"did","b":"have done","c":"should do","d":"have to do","answer":"3","explain":"\n-Should: used about a situation in the past when you said or knew what you would do or what would happen\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Firemen rescued several people from the ________ floor of the blazing building.","a":"high","b":"top","c":"basement","d":"low","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Top (floor): the highest floor","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"When the electricity failed, he ________ a match to find the candles.","a":"rubbed","b":"scratched","c":"struck","d":"started","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Strike a match: to produce a flame from a match by rubbing it hard across a rough surface.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"He filled in the necessary forms and ________ for the job.","a":"appealed","b":"asked","c":"requested","d":"applied","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Apply (for\/to) to make a formal request, usually written, for something such as a job, a place in a university, or permission to do something.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"She is traveling to work by train today because her car is being ________.","a":"stopped","b":"broken","c":"serviced","d":"rented","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Iif someone services a machine or vehicle, they examine it and do what is needed to keep it working well.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"}]}